Here.
I don't know if this'll help right away,
but go to the royal castle and show
this to the soldiers at the gate.
Now you can't do anything.
I'm going to take my time tormenting you.
All scoundrels think the same, huh?
38!
Have a pleasant trip.
Wait. What are your names?
Our names aren't worth mentioning.
On the road back to Muro,
I saved some troubled villagers
and defeated bandits attacking
a merchant before safely making it home.
I'm home.
Mimi!
That voice...
Welcome home.
You've grown so much, Teodorico.
Always a Catch!
Knight Captain
Episode 6
How the One That Got Away Fought With Her Father
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six! Seven! Eight!
I was raised differently from
my sisters for as long as I can remember.
21! 22!
23! 24!
25!
She's mastered forms one
through 25 at the age of three.
She's a genius.
The Annovazzi family has no boys.
An exception can be made so
a girl can inherit the title.
We should continue teaching
martial arts to Lady Maria.
Sir! Sir!
True...
BOOM
Maria, you'll be
the Annovazzi family heir.
Yes, Dad.
As they were no longer potential heirs,
my four sisters trained to be ladies
and found suitors in no time at all.
Meanwhile, even at my sisters' parties,
I was always surrounded by adults.
Having previously only
studied martial arts,
I began attending school
for nobles in middle school.
On my long-awaited first day of school...
Good morn...
How do you do?
Your makeup looks splendid again today.
When I saw the other ladies my age,
SHOCK
I realized how unrefined
my upbringing had been.
So Aida's not the only one
who says, "How do you do?"
How do you do?
Nice, Mimi.
None of the boys fancied me.
Score us a few more.
Instead, they treated me like one of them.
You're so cool, Mimi!
Every day, girls shrieked at me.
But as a duke's heir, I still had suitors.
They were obviously only
interested in my title, though.
That's when it happened.
What?
I'm having a little brother or sister?
That's right.
You'll be a big sister, too.
Would you prefer a brother or a sister?
I'd be happy to have either.
Several months after that...
He's so soft and warm.
F-Fantastic! I have an heir!
WHACK WHACK THUD THUD POW
You meathead!
Be more considerate!
Ow, ow, ow!
You suck!
How dare you treat your
own father this way!
Ow! Ow, that hurts!
Hold on. Uh, um...
The Annovazzi family's martial arts
are for protecting those dear to you.
I'll protect you forever.
Sorry.
Since little Teodorico was born,
I wasn't the heir anymore.
But honestly, I was glad.
After all, I'd always wanted to
be treated like a girl,
Let me carry that for you.
Let me carry
that for you
just like the other ladies.
Oh, my
Oh, my.
I had a late start, but if I
studied like them, then maybe...
I'd find a lovely fiancé.
Sister? What's wrong, Sister?
Everyone's waiting.
Let's go inside.
You're right.
It's not like me to feel anxious
about seeing my family.
Will they be truly glad about
my engagement to Prince Renato?
Welcome home, Mimi!
Idea, Nina,
Sandra, Gionna, and Mom.
RRRUMBLE...
Why didn't you come inside right away?
I mistook Macchio for you
and lifted him instead.
You didn't notice before then?
Sorry.
Forget that, Mimi. We're feasting tonight.
Crown Prince Bartolomey of Muro is coming.
You'd better thank him.
Hi, I'm Bart.
When the letter from Rubini arrived,
he's the one
who certified its authenticity.
He's just so considerate.
He has to be as Nina's husband, after all.
Did you say something, Sandra?
Mom, do we have any meat pies today?
Of course. I baked five just for today.
This feels like home.
Anyway, don't you have something to say?
Oh, uh, Prince Renato and I—
Not that.
I'm home, everyone!
Oh, right. I brought gifts for everyone.
Aida recommended some
perfumed oils and soaps.
Mimi...
Our Mimi's sitting with her legs together.
I never thought this day would come.
She's still drinking
vegetable juice, though.
Do you drink vegetable
juice in Rubini, too?
Anyway, I can't believe you
caught the crown prince of Rubini.
Prince Renato is
a wonderful man, isn't he?
I'm looking forward to meeting him.
Are you out of your mind, Mom?
I don't want to meet the crown
prince of a great kingdom.
He'll see right through us.
True. We don't know how to entertain him.
Our own kingdom's crown prince
is right here, you know.
The house is so lively
when everyone's here.
Welcome home, Mimi.
Lord Bartolomey,
have you met Prince Renato?
We've said hello.
He was beautiful and sincere.
But if he chose you,
he must be more than that.
He's right. There's something wrong
with Prince Renato and his kingdom
for accepting me as their future queen.
I can't fill Aida's shoes.
Maybe he chose you because
there's nobody like you.
It's like you read my mind.
Nina, I wanted to ask you
about marrying a crown prince.
Your wedding is on a much larger scale.
I'm not sure I can help.
I never thought you'd be drawn
to a man weaker than yourself.
He's not weaker.
Prince Renato's movements are elegant,
but I can't seem to avoid them.
Sometimes he's standing
behind me before I know it.
What?!
He can sneak up on you?!
He smiles all the time, but he's
so strong, I can't break his grip.
I've never met anyone like him.
I see.
I've heard of a legendary
group of assassins
with no gaps in their defenses
who can kill instantly.
Perhaps Prince Renato
is descended from them!
Summon all the instructors
first thing in the morning!
We must prepare for a counterattack!
What are you saying, Dad?
Sir, you mustn't kill the prince.
POUR
SIT...
Right.
That's right.
He's coming to negotiate a peace treaty.
He's coming to pay his respects
before the wedding.
Wedding?!
Is it just me, or is Dad acting weird?
He's still reeling from Mimi's engagement.
He's always weird, though.
I wanna play.
Sure, once you've finished
all the meat on your plate.
Drink your vegetable juice, too.
Okay.
Good boy, Teo.
Let's head outside before it gets dark.
Wait, Mimi! I'm not done talking to you!
The ogre's getting angry.
Run!
Hurry, hurry!
Always a Catch!
There! Up you go!
There!
Teo, 13!
Okay!
You're a genius!
Can we do Giant Swing next?
Sure thing!
Here we go!
We're not done yet!
I wanna sleep with you tonight.
Sure, of course.
All right!
Can you do the thing?
The funny face counting song.
Sure, of course.
I can't tell anyone "that" was the
start of my romance with the prince.
"That"
I should tell him
to keep it under wraps, too.
You know...
I can still only do up to form 18.
You can do 18 already? That's amazing.
Nuh-uh.
I heard you could do up to 25
when you were my age.
Who told you that?
It's okay. I'll try harder.
I'm sorry. You overheard me, didn't you?
Soon you'll grow a lot bigger
and stronger than me.
Really? I'll get bigger?
Of course you will.
As big as Dad?
Portrait of Father At Three Years Old
Probably, genetically speaking,
though it makes me sad.
RUB RUB RUB
May your legs grow
as long as Prince Renato's!
Who's Renato?
That man who's going to be my husband.
Is he strong?
Someday he'll be the most important
man in the Kingdom of Rubini.
CHATTER CHATTER
Wow!
Right?
He's really handsome and really nice.
RRRUMBLE...
Teo, could you go back inside?
Okay.
I can see you, you know.
Do you want to play with us, Dad?
N-No, of course not!
I thought I'd catch you unawares
to see if you're been training properly.
Are you really marrying
the crown prince of Rubini?
Yes.
I can't imagine an unrefined girl
like you becoming a crown princess.
I can't say I disagree.
On your guard.
In a foreign kingdom!
You'll be living
an unfamiliar life all alone!
Dad's blows are always
so heavy and quick.
I don't understand
what you're trying to say.
Our kingdoms may be neighbors,
but I won't be there
to help you right away!
I'm not alone!
I have the prince and Aida.
Everyone's really nice.
Everyone at the royal castle
protects me, too.
You allow yourself to be protected
by people weaker than you?
Yes.
Because I'll protect them so they
can protect me with peace of mind.
Besides, I was raised to be strong
enough to protect those dear to me...
SMILE!
by none other than you, Dad.
The Annovazzi family's martial arts
are for protecting those dear to you.
I don't understand.
But...
that's what makes you an Annovazzi.
Especially since Teo was born,
my father's always been
a bit hesitant around me.
But in reality,
he's arrogant and condescending,
with a big voice and bigger attitude,
and laughs with a mouth so wide
he'll swallow you whole.
Then let them protect
you without reservations.
Okay!
Just like this.
I told you to find a promising catch,
but you went way beyond that.
The second or third son of a middling
family would've been good enough.
Sorry. I guess I wasn't listening.
I never meant for you
to marry someone from abroad.
You know, Prince Renato said
he'll have this hairpin remade
based on the royal crest.
But I promise I'll keep the four rings.
After all, it'd be meaningless without it.
We finally settled on this design
after much disagreement.
It may change someday,
but I'll treasure it forever.
After all, I'm proud to have this.
I met the prince because you
allowed me to study abroad.
Thank you.
Sure.
I hope you'll give the prince
a proper welcome when he arrives.
You can count on it.
Excuse me, Your Highness.
I have urgent news.
What is it?
Just now...
Are you Lord Raimondo?
What? Uh, yes. Huh? What?
Some villagers from Navarro
arrived seeking my intervention.
They had a letter of introduction
from Count Falzone.
They also gave me
Lady Maria's handkerchief,
which had these dark red stains.
Dark red stains?
I thought it was blood
and had it analyzed.
It was grape juice.
Grape...
She must've been eating grapes.
Casually giving villagers
a stained handkerchief
sounds like something she'd do.
According to the villagers,
she introduced them to Count Falzone
and instructed them
to seek an audience with me.
Do Mimi and Count Falzone
share any kind of connection?
Lady Maria saved a merchant wagon
hired by the count from bandits.
I see. So, what do the villagers want?
Villager
Chief's Daughter
Their chief's daughter is missing,
but their lord refuses to help them.
Lord
Lady Maria helped them when they
were at their wit's end.
That's more or less what I was
told by a man with a heavy accent.
Who's the lord of Navarro Village?
Count Nardi.
Raimondo, we must leave this instant.
I've already made the arrangements.
Then I'll get to see Mimi soon.
What? Are you planning
to travel all night?
The village chief's daughter
is missing. We must hurry.
You're grinning.
To Be Continued
Translation: Sho Stifler
Timing: Mariana Martinez
Editing: Alicia Ashby
Quality Control: Ashley Barboza
Final Quality Control: Michelle Tymon
The queen dowager's doggy is really cute.
I used to have a pet, too.
It was cute and helped me practice.
It was a bear and not a dog,
but then Mom found out about it.
Next Time
The Fists of the One That Got Away
Oh, I spoke my mind again.